Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
- NMU (National Maritime Union of America), Publication (Box 622, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Plan NMU de Bienestares, Plan NMU de Pension, Plan NMU de Seguridad de Empleo, 1958; Publication (Box 622, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: NMU plan NMU de pension, Publication (Box 622, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Plan NMU de Bienestares, Publication (Box 622, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: NMU Pension Plan, Publication (Box 622, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: NMU Pension and Welfare Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 622, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: NMU Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 622, Folder 2)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Tell Your Congressperson No NAFTA, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
    Author: ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union)
  - Item 2: Los Solventes, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Support the Domsey Strikers, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: La Loi Dit, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: La Loi Dit, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: La Loi Dit, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Que Es La ILGWU?, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Que Es La ILGWU?, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Que Es La Union?, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
    Notes: Includes correspondence in English
  - Item 10: Chinese flyer about noise, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
    Language: Chinese.
  - Item 11: Chinese flyer, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Chinese flyer, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Chinese flyer, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Chinese booklet on fire safety, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Chinese booklet on cumulative trauma disorders, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Chinese booklet on cumulative trauma disorders, Publication (Box 622, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America. Eastern Conference of Teamsters., Publication (Box 622, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Manual for union organizers: revised 70, 1974; Publication (Box 622, Folder 4)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America. Eastern Conference of Teamsters.
  - Item 2: Sexual harassment: it's against the law: a Teamsters guide, Publication (Box 622, Folder 4)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 622, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Guide for IBEW Stewards, Publication (Box 622, Folder 5)
    Author: IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers)
- HERE (Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union); Culinary Workers Union, Local 226; Bartenders Union, Local 165, Publication (Box 622, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The American way to play is fair: Culinary Workers Union, Local 226, Bartenders Union, Local 165, 1988; Publication (Box 622, Folder 6)
    Author: HERE (Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union); Culinary Workers Union, Local 226; Bartenders Union, Local 165
- IWW (Industrial Workers of the World), Publication (Box 622, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Solidarity Forever, 2002; Publication (Box 622, Folder 7)
    Notes: Calendar
- IAM (International Association of Machinists), Publication (Box 622, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Your boss and the union as seen thru the eyes of a baby, Publication (Box 622, Folder 8)
    Author: IAM (International Association of Machinists)
- District 65 (Distributive Workers of America), Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Factual Data - 14th Convention, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
    Author: District 65 (Distributive Workers of America)
  - Item 2: Grievance procedure within the organization, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The District 65 employment office, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: District 65 Convention '76; Security plan, Pension plan, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: How 65'ers build a $150,000,000.00 (150 million dollar) Pension fund from 1950 to 1976, Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: A perspective for 65'ers outside the Metropolitan Area, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
    Author: Milton Reverby
  - Item 7: Report on re-structuring of the union, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
    Author: Frank Brown
  - Item 8: The role of the Steward, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Stewards manual the 65 security plan, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: article - A design for change, 1976; Publication (Box 622, Folder 9)
    Author: David Livingston
- HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 622, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Catering Industry Employee, 1990; Publication (Box 622, Folder 10)
    Author: HERE (Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union)
    Notes: v.99:no.8 (1990:Aug.)
    Language: English;French;Spanish.
  - Item 2: Catering Industry Employee, 1990; Publication (Box 622, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.99:no.8 (1990:Aug.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Catering Industry Employee, 1990; Publication (Box 622, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.99:no.10 (1990:Oct.)
  - Item 4: Catering Industry Employee, 1990; Publication (Box 622, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.99:no.10 (1990:Oct.). Copy 2.
- Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York, Publication (Box 623, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Rep Handbook, Publication (Box 623, Folder 1)
    Author: Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York
- Pennsylvania Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 623, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: President's report to the Harrisburg Convention: 1921, Publication (Box 623, Folder 2)
    Author: James H. Maurer
- OCAW (Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union), Publication (Box 623, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Understanding our history, 1994; Publication (Box 623, Folder 3)
    Author: OCAW (Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 623, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Pension benefit manual, Publication (Box 623, Folder 4)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 623, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Resource manual for New Officers & Staff, Publication (Box 623, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.2
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 623, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Healthcare benefits bargaining manual, Publication (Box 623, Folder 6)
- National Post Office Mail Handlers, Publication (Box 623, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 1990 Contract Action Campaign Manual, Publication (Box 623, Folder 7)
    Author: National Post Office Mail Handlers
- OCAW (Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union), Publication (Box 623, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Handbook for OCAW women, 1973; Publication (Box 623, Folder 8)
    Author: Katherine Stone
- NYSUT (New York State United Teachers), Publication (Box 623, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Annual NYSUT Community College Conference (23rd, 24th), 2001-2002 (Box 623, Folder 9)
- NYSNA (New York State Nurses Association), Publication (Box 623, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Function & structure: who we are, how to tap our resources, ways to be involved, 2000; Publication (Box 623, Folder 10)
    Author: NYSNA (New York State Nurses Association)
- NYSNA (New York State Nurses Association), Publication (Box 623, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: NYSNA Delegate Assembly: Rules, 1999; Publication (Box 623, Folder 11)
- UFT (United Federation of Teachers), Publication (Box 624, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: United Federation of Teachers: Chapter Leader: Handbook, 1989; Publication (Box 624, Folder 1)
    Author: UFT (United Federation of Teachers)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Women's Department Report: 1970 Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 624, Folder 2)
    Author: Caroline Davis
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Women's Department Report: 1968 Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 624, Folder 3)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Women's Department Report, April 1972, Publication (Box 624, Folder 4)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: UAW Women's Department 25th Anniversary, 1955-1980, Publication (Box 624, Folder 5)
    Author: UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: UAW Policy established by Convention Resolutions relative to Women workers' rights, 1968; Publication (Box 624, Folder 6)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Women's Rights Resolution; 24th Constitutional Convention, 1974; Publication (Box 624, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Women's Rights Resolution; 24th Constitutional Convention, 1974; Publication (Box 624, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Resolutions Committee, Report on Women's Rights - 24th Constitutional Convention, 1974; Publication (Box 624, Folder 7)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Eighth Annual International Women's Conference., 1981; Publication (Box 624, Folder 8)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Have you just been elected? Duties of Women's Committee Officers and Rules for Conducting Meetings, Publication (Box 624, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Have you just been elected or appointed? Duties of Women's Committee Officers and Rules for Conducting Meetings, 1978; Publication (Box 624, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Have you just been elected? Duties of Women's Committee Officers and Rules for Conducting Meetings, 1969; Publication (Box 624, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Have you just been elected? Duties of Women's Committee Officers and Rules for Conducting Meetings, 1969; Publication (Box 624, Folder 9)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: He learned about women from his Shop Steward, Publication (Box 624, Folder 10)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Public Review Board; 32nd Annual Report, 1989; Publication (Box 624, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Public Review Board; 33rd Annual Report, 1990; Publication (Box 624, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Public Review Board; 35th Annual Report, 1992; Publication (Box 624, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Public Review Board; 36th Annual Report, 1993; Publication (Box 624, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Public Review Board; 37th Annual Report, 1994; Publication (Box 624, Folder 11)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Affirmative Action Program for Apprenticeship Training, 1980; Publication (Box 624, Folder 12)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Maintain your health wile you're unemployed, 1992; Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: UAW Community Services in the local union, 1992; Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Community Services; Forebearance, 1991; Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: UAW Community Services; Strike Assistance Committees, 1987; Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Lend a Hand; UAW EAP Manual, 1990; Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: UAW Strike Assitance Program: a handbook for Local Union Community Services Committee Chairmen, 1988; Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Tough times, tough decisions: Community Services Guide, 1991; Publication (Box 624, Folder 13)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A Few Facts About: Energy, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: A Few Facts About: Human Rights, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: A Few Facts About: Inflation, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: A Few Facts About: National Health Insurance, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: A Few Facts About: Taxes and Tax Reform, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: The Fight for Jobs, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Strength in Bargaining '79, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: To Win Progress for People, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: To Win Progress for People, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Bargaining at the Main Table, 1979; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Entering the job market: a workbook on how to become a successful job applicant, 1984; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Entering the job market: (Discussion Leader's Outline): a workbook on how to become a successful job applicant, 1984; Publication (Box 624, Folder 14)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: UAW, National Collective Bargaining Convention: Resolution-1979, Collective Bargaining Program: April 17-18, 1979, Cobo Hall, Michigan, Publication (Box 624, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: History of Local #564 of the International Union United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Implement Workers of America, C.I.O., 1948; Publication (Box 624, Folder 15)
    Author: Nelson M. Ripley
  - Item 3: The Lonely Millionaire, 1949; Publication (Box 624, Folder 15)
    Author: John MacLeod; Bob Scott
    Notes: News clipping. Photocopy
  - Item 4: Wilson Home, Sought as Chancery, 1949; Publication (Box 624, Folder 15)
    Author: Lance Zavite
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America). Local 259, Publication (Box 624, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Local 259: United Automobile Workers of America, 1983; Publication (Box 624, Folder 16)
    Author: Margo Nash
- Transport Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 624, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Rising cost of presecription drugs: resolution submitted, Publication (Box 624, Folder 17)
    Author: Sonny Hall
    Notes: Resolution submitted to the AFL-CIO Executive Council
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 624, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Volunteer Organizer, Publication (Box 624, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Textile Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 624, Folder 18)
    Notes: v.24:no.2 (1963:Feb.)
- Local 5, Independent, Publication (Box 625, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: election flyer -- 5 for 5, 1949; Publication (Box 625, Folder 1)
    Author: Local 5, Independent
- Local 1199, Publication (Box 625, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Draft - Local 1199 Political Action Program, Publication (Box 625, Folder 2)
    Author: Local 1199
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1953; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1955; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1978; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1984; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Consitution and by-laws, 1960; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Consitution and by-laws, 1962; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Consitution and by-laws, 1964; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Consitution and by-laws, 1966; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Consitution and by-laws, 1970; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Consitution and by-laws, 1972; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Agreement and plan of merger and consolidation, 1976; Publication (Box 625, Folder 3)
    Author: ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 625, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Journal of Electrical Workers and Operators, 1926; Publication (Box 625, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.25:no.2 (1926:Feb.
- Building Laborers International Union of America, Publication (Box 625, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Building Laborers International Union of America, Publication (Box 625, Folder 5)
    Author: Building Laborers International Union of America
  - Item 2: Local Assembly 6512, Knights of Labor, Publication (Box 625, Folder 5)
    Author: Knights of Labor
  - Item 3: Laborers' Protective Union, Publication (Box 625, Folder 5)
    Author: Laborers' Protective Union
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 625, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The dispute now going on within the ranks of the needle trades workers of New York has called attention again to the outworn constitution of the ILGWU, 1926; Publication (Box 625, Folder 6)
    Notes: Press release. Photocopy.
- Cloakmakers and Furriers, Publication (Box 625, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Joint Defense and Relief committee Cloakmakers and Furriers - To All workers' organizaitons, 1927; Publication (Box 625, Folder 7)
    Author: Cloakmakers and Furriers
- HERE (Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union), Publication (Box 625, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Washington Update, 1983; Publication (Box 625, Folder 8)
    Author: HERE (Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1983:Feb.)
  - Item 2: Washington Update, 1983; Publication (Box 625, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1983:Apr.)
  - Item 3: Washington Update, 1983; Publication (Box 625, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1983:Sep.)
  - Item 4: Washington Update, 1984; Publication (Box 625, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1984:Jan.)
  - Item 5: Washington Update, Publication (Box 625, Folder 8)
    Notes: Special Supplement: Tip Reporting
- USWA (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 625, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania labor history: a reading list, Publication (Box 625, Folder 9)
    Author: USWA (United Steelworkers of America)
- UTU (United Transportation Union), Publication (Box 625, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Man on the Move - Cliff Merritt's Scrapbook, Publication (Box 625, Folder 10)
- UFCW (United Food and Commercial Workers International Union), Publication (Box 625, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: UFCW economic dislocation manual, Publication (Box 625, Folder 11)
    Author: UFCW (United Food and Commercial Workers International Union)
- UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union), Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Dioxins in the workplace paperworkers respond, 1989; Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
    Author: UPIU (United Paperworkers International Union)
    Notes: Reprinted from The Paperworker, January, 1989.
  - Item 2: A troublemaker's handbook, Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
    Author: Labor Notes
  - Item 3: Why should my local joint the IP bargaining pool?, Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: The talk now, Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: If your child needs medical attention, will it be there?, Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Turning Democracy upside down!, Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: A union member's guide to International Paper Company: United Paperworkers International Union, 1991; Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: When all else fails!: enforcement of the Emergency Planning and Community Right-to-Know Act: a self help manual for local emergency planning committees, 1989; Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
    Author: EPA (Environmental Protection Agency)
  - Item 9: Chemicals in your community: a guide to the Emergency Planning and Community Right-to-Know Act, 1988; Publication (Box 625, Folder 12)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 625, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Women's Department Report: 1980 UAW Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 625, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: UAW Women's Department Resolutions Adopted at the 26th Constitutional Convention, 1980; Publication (Box 625, Folder 13)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 625, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Women in society and 50th Anniversary of Woman's right to votefrom 22nd Constitutional convention, 1970; Publication (Box 625, Folder 14)
- UE (United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America), Publication (Box 625, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Proposed Resolutions and Amendments, 1974; Publication (Box 625, Folder 15)
- UFW (United Farm Workers); A. Philip Randolph Institute, Publication (Box 625, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Right to work laws, a trap for America's minorities. El derecho a trabajar: una trampa para los minorias EE.UU, 1968; Publication (Box 625, Folder 16)
    Author: Bayard Rustin; Cesar E. Chavez
- UNITE!, Publication (Box 626, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Remembering Joseph Fisher, Publication (Box 626, Folder 1)
    Author: Pennsylvania, Ohio and South Jersey Joint Board
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Special convention: Committees, 1995; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Author: ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union)
  - Item 2: United in purpose, united in action, 1988; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 4, 1990
  - Item 4: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 4, 1990. Copy 2.
  - Item 5: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 5, 1990
  - Item 6: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 5, 1990. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 6, 1990
  - Item 8: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 6, 1990. Copy 2.
  - Item 9: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 7, 1990
  - Item 10: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 7, 1990. Copy 2.
  - Item 11: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 8, 1990
  - Item 12: Convention unity, 1990; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 5th Constitutional Convention, June 8, 1990. Copy 2.
  - Item 13: Convention unity, 1993; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 6th Constitutional Convention, June 7, 1993
  - Item 14: Convention unity, 1993; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 6th Constitutional Convention, June 8, 1993
  - Item 15: Convention unity, 1993; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 6th Constitutional Convention, June 9, 1993
  - Item 16: Convention unity, 1993; Publication (Box 627, Folder 1)
    Notes: 6th Constitutional Convention, June 10, 1993